<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BPL BeWell</string>
    <string name="my_profile">My Profile</string>
    <string name="log_profile">Login Profile</string>
    <string name="user_guide">User\'s Guide</string>


    <string name="app_version">App Version</string>
    <string name="selection">Select your Device</string>
    <string name="select_option">Select Any Option</string>
    <string name="logout">LogOut</string>

    
    <string name="ioxy">BPLBeWell iOxy</string>
    <string name="weigh_mc">BPLBeWell iWeigh</string>
    <string name="bp">BPLBeWell iPressure BT02</string>
      <!--user details strings-->
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="age">Age (Years)</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="height">Height(cm)</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight(kg)</string>
    <string name="set_name">Set Name</string>
    <string name="set_age">Set Age</string>

    <string name="set_address">Set City</string>
    <string name="user_name">User Name</string>
    <string name="ad_name">Login Name</string>
    <string name="set_phone">Set Phone No.</string>
    <string name="set_email">Set Email</string>

    <string name="set_height">Set Height</string>
    <string name="set_weight">Set Weight</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>

    <string name="new_user">New User</string>
    <string name="exist_user">Existing User</string>


    <string name="ch_sel_user">Edit Selected User Info</string>
    <string name="switch_user">Switch User</string>

    <string name="sure_sel_user">Are you Sure you want to delete Selected Records</string>

    <string name="address">City</string>
    <string name="add_user">Add New User</string>
    <string name="sel_user">Select User</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone No.</string>

    <string name="edit_user">Edit User</string>

    <string name="security_ver">Enter the Security Questions for verification</string>

    <string name="spo2high"> Spo2 High</string>
    <string name="spo2low">Spo2 Low</string>
    <string name="heart_rate_high">Pulse Rate High</string>
    <string name="heart_rate_low">Pulse Rate Low</string>
    <string name="pi_high">PI High</string>
    <string name="pi_low">PI Low</string>

    <string name="security_question_1">Select your favourite color</string>
    <string name="security_question_2">Select your Date Of Birth</string>
    <string name="security_question_3">Select your Use Type</string>
    <string name="security_question_3_">Use type</string>


  <string name="user_guide_content">BPL Be Well App User Guide\n\n
1.       Connecting your mobile phone with BPL iOxy device:\n
To connect your mobile with BPL iOxy device, please follow the below steps\n
a)	Before connecting the BPL iOxy device to your mobile through Bluetooth, turn on the BPl iOxy device and place your finger
      into the slot provided. Wait until the data is displayed on BPL iOxy device’s screen post which you can establish the
      Bluetooth connection.\n
b)      Launch BPL Be Well App that is installed on your mobile.\n
c)	Create a personal login by Signing Up. \n
d)	Add a profile by entering your personal details. \n
e)	Tap on Connect to initiate Bluetooth Connection. \n
f)	Allow the App to Turn On Bluetooth on your mobile device. \n
g)      Tap on Search button to scan for the BPL iOxy device.\n
h)      Choose the ‘BPL iOxy’ from the displayed list of devices.\n\n
After following the above steps, real time data would be displayed.\n\n
Note: BPL iOxy device will automatically turn off if no signal is received within 10 seconds.\n\n
2.       Usage steps:\n
a)       After connecting your mobile to the device through Bluetooth, the data will be displayed on your BPL iOxy Application
        screen.\n
b)      After the connection, real time data of “Blood Oxygen (SPO2)”, “Pulse Rate (PR)” and “Perfusion Index (PI)”
        will be displayed.\n
c)       The application will record the monitoring results and displays with time range on your mobile phone.\n
d)	To start a measurement, Tap on the “START RECORDING” button.
Note: Ensure that at least 40 seconds has elapsed before you press on STOP RECORDING” for a record to get saved. \n
e) 	To save this measurement, Tap on the “STOP RECORDING” button.
        The App shall generate a record which includes “report” and “trend chart”.\n
Note: Multiple Users can monitor and save measurements using dedicated logins.
        Verify your user profile before taking measurements.\n\n
3.       Application use:\n
With the help of this App, the real time results can be synchronised with the device and shown on the
        smart phone for a better user experience. Using the smartphone, the user information can be edited and
        reports can be reviewed at any point of time.\n
User Info: To Edit user’s name, age, height, and weight. New Users can be added at any point of time.\n
User Guide: For App usage assistance\n\n
4.       Health Parameters measured:\n
a)       Oxy-haemoglobin Saturation: Oxygen Saturation (SPO2) is a term which refers to the concentration of oxygen
        in the blood. It measures the percentage of haemoglobin binding sites in the blood stream occupied by Oxygen,
        which is a very important physiological parameter of respiration cycle. The normal range of blood oxygen
        levels is considered to be 95-100 percent. Between 90-95 percent, the blood oxygen level is considered to be
        low but it does not necessarily indicate any health issue.\n
b)      Pulse Rate: Pulse, also known as heart rate is the number of times the heart beats per minute.
        Normally, pulse rate and heart rate are identical. The Pulse rate range for a healthy person would be 60-90
        bpm. Nervousness and an excited state of being may increase the pulse rate/heart rate.\n
c)       Perfusion Index: Perfusion index or PI is the ratio of the pulsatile blood flow to the non-pulsatile
        static blood flow in a peripheral tissue, such as fingertip, toe, or ear lobe. Perfusion Index is an
        indication of pulse strength at the sensor site. The PI value ranges from 0.02 percent for a very weak pulse
        to 20 percent for a very strong pulse. The Pi value varies depending on the users, physiological conditions,
        and monitoring sites. For a healthy user, the value of PI would be greater than three percent.\n\n
5.       About this software:\n
BPL Be Well app is designed and developed by BPL Medical Technologies Pvt. Ltd for the device BPL iOxy. This application is compatible with mobile phones with the operating system Android 4.3 (Or above).\n
</string>


    <string name="oxy_saturation_report">Oxyhemoglobin Saturation Report</string>
    
    
    <string name="spo2">Spo2</string>
    <string name="spo2_machine">measure Spo2 and its related parameters</string>
    <string name="weigh_machine">measure weighing machine</string>
    <string name="records">list of records</string>
    <string name="baseline">Base Line</string>
    <string name="duration">Duration</string>
    <string name="event">Event</string>
    <string name="minimum">Minimum</string>
    <string name="low_oxy_avg">Low Oxyhaemoglobin average  —</string>
    <string name="pulse_rate">Pulse Rate</string>
    <string name="avg_bp_min">Average(bpm/min)</string>
    <string name="min_bp_min">Minimum(bpm/min)</string>
    
    <string name="spo2_range">Spo2 Range</string>
    <string name="analysis">Analysis</string>
    <string name="pulse_rate_event">Pulse Rate Event</string>
    <string name="plethysmogram">Plethysmogram</string>
    <string name="testing_time">Testing Time</string>
    <string name="user_info">User Information:</string>
    <string name="device_mac_id">Device Name</string>

    <string name="range_1">99–90</string>
    <string name="range_2">89–80</string>
    <string name="range_3">79–70</string>
    <string name="range_4">69–60</string>
    <string name="range_5">59–50</string>
    <string name="range_6">49–40</string>
    <string name="range_7">39–30</string>

    <string name="user_name_">Enter User Name</string>
    <string-array name="search_by">
        <item> Name</item>
        <item> Phone</item>


    </string-array>

    <string name="connect_device">Switch On BPL iOxy device.Tap on Connect </string>
    <string name="disconnect_device">Do you want to exit BPL iOxy measurement ?</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="search_by_name">Search By User Name</string>
    <string name="search_by_phone">Search By Phone No.</string>

    <string name="different_user">Sign in with a different account</string>
    <string name="ble_not_supported">This device doesn\'t support Bluetooth Low Energy</string>
    <string name="start_rec">Start Recording</string>
    <string name="stop_rec">Stop Recording</string>

    <string name="record_not_saved">Please wait atleast 40 sec in order to save current records</string>
    <string name="app_version_str">The current app version you are using is </string>
    <string name="field_empty">This field cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="search_bpl_dev">Connecting to BPL iOxy device…</string>

    <string name="proceed">Proceed</string>
    <string name="background_image">Background Image</string>
    <string name="back">Back key</string>
    <string name="base_header_title">Base header title</string>
    <string name="verify">Verify</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password ?</string>
    <string name="user_guide_">User Guide</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log In</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="security_ques">Security Question</string>
    <string name="submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="manage_user">MANAGE USER</string>

    <string name="update">UPDATE</string>


    <string name="bpl_moto">Happier Living Everyday</string>
    <string name="spo_percentage">SPO2 (%)</string>
    <string name="pr_bpm">Pulse Rate(bpm)</string>
    <string name="pi">PI</string>
    <string name="report">Report</string>
    <string name="chart">Chart</string>

    <string name="speaker_img">Speaker to enable alarm or not</string>
    <string name="record_img">To capture records</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_img">Indicator to know whether bluetooth is connected or not</string>
    <string name="action_report">generate selected report</string>
    <string name="action_report_chart">generate report chart of selected records</string>
    <string name="high">High</string>
    <string name="bluetooth">BLUETOOTH</string>
    <string name="select">Select</string>
    <string name="reset_pwd">RESET PASSWORD</string>
    <string name="help">HELP</string>

    <string name="records_weigh_a">RECORDS I-WEIGH 1</string>

    <string name="weight_">Weight in kg</string>
    <string name="bmi">BMI</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>

    <string name="bio_text">** Sit down and Wear the BPL iPressure as shown.\n** Relax and Switch ON the device.
            </string>


    <string name="weigh_machine_manual_1">1. Place the scale on a hard and flat surface. Gently step on it, and
it turns on with digits display on the LED. Then step off the scale
until the value on the LED displays zero. Step on it again in an
upright and steady position. See the picture below for the correct
standing position.\n\n 2. The weight value on the display will flash three times. Do not
read it until it stabilizes.\n\n

        <b>Converting Weight Units</b>\n\n
The factory default unit is kg. For unit conversion, open the
battery cover at the back when power-off and adjust the gear
toggle switch. The units available are kg and lb  from
left to right. When the switch is placed at one of the gears, the
displayed unit automatically switches to the corresponding
weight unit after the scale is turned on.\n\n
        The unit conversion toggle switch is located inside the battery
case at the back of the scale.

    </string>


    <string name="logout_content">Are you sure want to LogOut?</string>



    <string name="biolight">BPLBeWell iPressure BT02</string>


    <string name="bio_user_guide">

       <b>Preparation before measurement</b>\n\n


(1)	Keep your body and mood calm, take off the thicker clothes such as coat,
 sweater, Etc. When measuring, bare upper arm or wear thinner shirt.\n

(2)	Users, who use APP software, need to open the Bluetooth of the device and terminal,
 open the APP software, and connect with the device.\n\n


When a call comes in during the measurement, the measurement will be terminated.
It is recommended that Android  device be set in airplane mode during measurement to avoid strong magnetism interference.



•	Using Steps\n
•	Apply the cuff\n


1.	Loosen the calibre of the curly cuff slightly. Place a bare arm through the cuff directly according to
 the instruction\n

2.	Position the cuff 1-2cm above the elbow joint and ensure the mark  on the cuff shall lie above artery.\n


3.	Pull one end of the cuff to the lateral and tighten. The cuff should fit comfortably, yet snugly
        around your arm. You should be able to insert one finger between your arm and the cuff.\n\n


Body posture\n\n


  Stay still and calm for five minutes before taking a blood pressure measurement.
  Be seated with your feet flat on the floor without crossing your legs.
  Place your hand palm-side up in front of you on a flat surface such as a desk or table.
  The cuff should be placed at the same level as your heart.\n\n

	<b>NOTE : </b>\n\n

	Incorrect measuring posture showed as follows might cause an incorrect measurement:\n
	Bent over（lean forward）;\n
	Sitting cross-legged;\n
	Bend the body because of the low table or sitting on sofa.\n\n



•	Measuring\n

•	Short press (press and hold it less than 2s) the power button to turn on the device, then the cuff pressure
        automatically and the screen shows rising pressure values. Stay still and calm during measurement.
        Do not move your arm, body and the device.\n\n

•	You can press the select users button “   ” to select user.
        If you need to change the user during measurement, short press (press and hold it less than 2s)
        the power button to stop the measurement. Then press the button “   ” to select user. Short press
        (press and hold it less than 2s) the power button again to continue the measurement.\n\n
•	Display the measurement value\n

•	The device exhausts automatically and displays the measurement results.
        About the display interface of measurement results, please refer to chapter “Display ”.\n\n

•	Users, who use the APP software, can read the measurement results on the software interface.\n

•	Take off the cuff\n
•	Turn off the device\n

•	Long press (press and hold it more than 2s) the power button to turn off the device after the measurement.\n\n

•	<b>NOTE :</b>\n\n

   While measuring blood pressure, the users must stay still and calm without any talk;
  The cuff tied on the limb shall be on the same level as the patient’s
  heart so as to avoid the reading error resulting from the hydrostatics effect of the blood
  flow between the heart and cuff. If the cuff position is higher than heart level, the BP reading will be
  lower, the measured result shall be added 0.75mmHg\n\n

   (0.1kPa) for each centimeter higher; in case the cuff position is lower than heart level,
   the BP reading will be higher, the measured result shall be deducted 0.75mmHg (0.1kPa) for each centimeter lower;
   If the signal measurement time is more than two minutes and the device doesn’t exhaust automatically,
    please take off the cuff and turn off the device.\n\n



   You can stop the measurement process at any time by pressing “Start/Stop” button.\n\n




  Prolonged and frequent BPL iPressure BT02 measurements are associated with ischemia and neuropathy
  in the limb wearing the cuff. Please examine the extremities of the limb frequently for normal color, warmth and
  sensitivity. If any abnormality is observed, stop the BPL iPressure BT02 measurements.\n

  Too frequent measurements may have influence on the measurement results.\n\n


    </string>
    <string name="searc">Search</string>
    <string name="blu">BLUETOOTH</string>
    <string name="sear">Search</string>
    <string name="sear_">Search…</string>
    <string name="res">Result</string>
    <string name="mark_all">Mark All</string>


    <string name="mark_all_active_users">Mark All Active Users</string>
    <string name="mark_all_dormant_users">Mark All Dormant Users</string>
    <string name="save_as_png">save as PNG</string>
    <string name="pick_col">Pick a color</string>
    <string name="share_as_png">Share as PNG</string>
    <string name="sha">Share</string>
    <string name="export_users">Export Users</string>
    <string name="visc_fat">Visceral Fat</string>
    <string name="body_fat">Body Fat</string>
    <string name="bmr">BMR</string>
    <string name="metabolic_age">Metabolic Age</string>
    <string name="body_water">Body Water</string>
    <string name="weight_in_kg">Weight in Kg</string>
    <string name="bmi_statistics">BMI STATISTICS</string>
    <string name="bmi_text1">BMI change since last 7 days : 0.2 %</string>
    <string name="bmi_text2">BMI change since last 30 days : 1.0%</string>
    <string name="tap_to_know_more_about_bmi">Tap to Know more about BMI</string>


    <string name="bpm">BPM</string>
    <string name="mm_hg">mmHg</string>
    <string name="kpa">kPa</string>
    <string name="pul_rate">Pulse Rate</string>
    <string name="normal_">Normal</string>
    <string name="pre_hypertension">PreHypertension</string>
    <string name="hypertension">Hypertension</string>

    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="rec_saved">Current Record Saved</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>

    <string name="comment">Comment</string>


    <string name="unit">Unit Selected</string>
    <string name="voice">Voice</string>


    <string name="sound_desirable">According to world health Organization , the blood pressure level
    of your body is desirable</string>

    <string name="sound_normal">According to world health Organization , the blood pressure level
    of your body is normal</string>

    <string name="sound_pre_hyper">According to world health Organization , the blood pressure level
    of your body is pre hypertension</string>
    <string name="sound_mild_hyper">According to world health Organization , the blood pressure level
    of your body is Mild hypertension</string>

    <string name="sound_moderate_hyper">According to world health Organization , the blood pressure level
    of your body is Moderate hypertension</string>

    <string name="sound_low">According to world health Organization , the blood pressure level
    of your body is low</string>

    <string name="sound_severe_hypertension">According to world health Organization , the blood pressure level
    of your body is Severe hypertension</string>



    <string name="severe_hypertension">Grade 3 Severe Hypertension</string>
    <string name="moderate_hypertension">Grade 2 Moderate Hypertension</string>
    <string name="mild_hypertension">Grade 1 Mild Hypertension</string>
    <string name="high_normal">High Normal</string>
    <string name="optimal">Optimal</string>
    <string name="low">Low</string>
    <string name="sys_by_dia">(SYS / DIA)</string>
    <string name="action_delete">delete the records</string>
    <string name="delete_rec">Do you want to delete the record ?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="del_rec">Delete Record</string>
    <string name="record">Records</string>
    <string name="trend">Trend</string>
    <string name="exit_user_log">Select Existing User </string>


    <string name="blood_press">Blood Pressure</string>
    <string name="measuring">Measuring …</string>


    <string name="bio_light_err_cuff">Check whether cuff is damaged or leaky, wrap cuff correctly refer to users manual and measure again
    </string>
    <string name="hide">Hide Values</string>
    <string name="sho">Show Values</string>

    <string name="share_via">Share Via</string>
    <string name="cancel_">Cancel</string>
    <string name="title_header">Title Header</string>
    <string name="stp_">Stop</string>
    <string name="day">Day</string>
    <string name="month">Month</string>
    <string name="week">Week</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="body_age">Body Age</string>
    <string name="metabolism">Metabolism</string>
    <string name="bone_mass">Bone \n Mass</string>
    <string name="muscle_mass">Muscle Mass</string>
    <string name="lbm">LBM</string>
    <string name="obesity">Obesity</string>
    <string name="pulse_min_vs_time">Pulse/min Vs Time</string>
    <string name="bp_mmhg_vs_date">BP(mmHg Vs Date)</string>
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="pul_mm_hg">PUL(mmHg)</string>
    <string name="dia_mm_hg">DIA(mmHg)</string>
    <string name="sys_mm_hg">SYS(mmHg)</string>
    <string name="protein">Protein</string>


    <string name="muscle_mass_str">Muscle mass index is calculated from muscle mass, body weight and height
    It is a quantitative assesment of health, status and strength</string>

    <string name="protein_str">Protein is an important component of human cells and the organization,
    accounting for about 18% of the total mass of the human body. Large numbers of protein are contained
    in muscle cells, which is the main factors that reflect the nutritional status, physical development
    and health of the person being tasted</string>

    
    
    <string name="body_age_str">Body Age is calculated based on basal metabolism. And the basal metabolism is the
    comprehensive weight,body fat rate, muscle rate and other indexes. So the age of the body is a measure 
        of the physical condition of a person who is above and below the actual age.
        In other words is the criteria for judging the condition of the body . Even the height and weight of the 
        surveyors are the same, because differences in body fat and basal metabolic rate also lead to differences in age
        
    </string>
    
    
<string name="metabolism_str">Basal Metabolism is the minimal rate of energy expenditure unit time by
    animals at rest. It was measured under the circumstances when a man is awake and at complete rest
</string>

<string name="bone_mass_str">The human skeleton, composed of bones, supports the human body.
Bone mineral density and calcium loss are the main concerns of bone health.
</string>


<string name="body_water_str"> Body Water percentage, is closely related to body muscle mass, since muscle
contains a large amount of water. (approx 70%)</string>

    <string name="body_fat_str"> Fat percentage is the total mass of fat divided by total body mass.
    It provides a better assessment for how fat or thin a person is compared to BMI
    </string>


    <string name="lbm_str">Also known as lean body weight, which is the weight of the body composition
    except the fat. Muscle is one of the main part of the fat body weight. The more developed the muscle is
    , the better physical fitness is
    </string>


    <string name="visceral_fat_str">Visceral Fat is fat stored within abdominal cavity around a number of
    internal organs</string>
    <string name="bone_mass_">Bone Mass</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="edit_prof">EDIT PROFILE</string>
    <string name="add_prof">ADD PROFILE</string>
    <string name="add_clinic_prof">Add CLINIC PROFILE</string>
    <string name="man_fam_men">Manage Family Member</string>
    <string name="mem_name">Member Name</string>
    <string name="set_family_memeber_name">Set Member Name</string>
    <string name="add_fam_mem">Add Family Member</string>
    <string name="up_fam_mem">Update Family Member</string>
    <string name="mana_fam_mem">MANAGE  FAMILY MEMBER</string>
    <string name="terms_cond"> I understand and accept the "Terms and Conditions and "Privacy Consent"</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition">Terms And Condition</string>
    <string name="sel_fam_mem">Select Family Member</string>
    <string name="edt_fam_mem">Edit Selected User Info</string>
    <string name="ok_">OK</string>
    <string name="curr_app">The current app version is</string>



    <string name="terms_and_conditions">These Terms and Conditions (“Terms”/ or “Agreement”) govern use of the BPL BE WELL  software, including any updates or supplements thereto (“Application”)
that is downloaded, installed onto the user mobile devices and/or used by Consumers and or Users only through the Application developed and
home care Device/s manufactured and or marketed by BPL MEDICAL TECHNOLOGIES PRIVATE LIMITED, a company incorporated and registered in India
and having its registered office at 11th  KM, Bannerghatta Road, Arakere, BANGALORE-560 076, Karnataka, India and its affiliates ("BPL Medtech”).\n

BPL Medtech allows limited use of the Application to Users on their mobile devices on the basis of this terms and subject to any rules or
policies applied by any appstore provider, such as but not limited to the Apple AppStore , the Google Play Store (Third Party Rules) or any other App software
distribution repository. BPL Medtech  does not sell the Application to Users or Consumers. BPL
        Medtech remains the owner of the Application at all times.\n\n

1.	Use of the Application.\n

By clicking the "I Accept" checkbox  at the end of these Terms or by making use of  the Application with Device, the Users agrees and acknowledges that
the Users have read, understood and consented to the terms and conditions and agrees to be bound by these Terms. The Users may use the Application  only with
BPL Medtech Device for such purposes as is set out in Agreement. The use of BPL Medtech Application is available only to persons who can form legally binding
contracts under the Indian Contract Act, 1872.These Terms may be changed at any time without any prior notice to the Users. The Users continued use of the
Application after any such change constitutes the Users acceptance and acknowledgement of the new Terms. If the Users does not agree to abide by these or
any future Terms, please do not use the Application. \n\n

USERS  UNDERSTAND THAT THE APPLICATION IS PROVIDED ‘AS IS’ AND THAT IT IS NOT INTENDED TO AMOUNT TO ANY ADVICE\n

INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO MEDICAL ADVICE, OR FOR DIAGNOSTIC PURPOSES ON WHICH RELIANCE SHOULD BE PLACED. BPL MEDITCH IS NOT A MEDICAL CARE
PROVIDER AND DO NOT PROVIDE MEDICAL ADVICE. THE APPLICATION IS NOT INTENDED TO BE RELIED UPON IN LIEU OF MEDICAL TREATMENT OR ADVICE BY A TRAINED
 MEDICAL CARE PROVIDER. ALWAYS CONSULT YOUR DOCTOR OR OTHER HEALTHCARE PROFESSIONAL WITH ANY QUESTIONS REGARDING ANY MEDICAL CONDITION, OR FOR SPECIFIC
 GUIDANCE REGARDING NUTRITION OR PHYSICAL ACTIVITY.\n\n

The Application may contain links to or provide a connectivity functionality with other independent third-party websites or device applications
(Third-party Sites). These Third-party Sites are not under BPL Medtech control, and BPL Medtech is not responsible for and do not endorse their content,
their data privacy governance and/or their privacy policies (if any). User will need to make their own independent judgement regarding their interaction
 with any Third-party Sites, including the purchase and use of any products or services accessible through them.
Any words following the terms including, include, in particular or for example or any similar
phrase shall be construed as illustrative and shall not limit the generality of the related general words.\n\n

2. Download\n

All Users will be required to download the Application, review the terms stated in the agreement, agree to abide by the Terms stated, read and
understand the contents of the User’s manual before using the BPL Medtech Device. Each Users represents that he/she is of the legal age of majority
and can enter into binding contracts. If a minor is making use of the Application with Devices, then the download and installed on his/her mobile device
solely for the purposes shall be done by his / her parent or legal guardian who agrees to abide by these Terms. Where a minor download the Application
 and uses the BPL Medtech Devices, his / her parent or legal guardian alone shall be responsible for all purposes pertaining to the use of the Application
 along with BPL Medtech Device and all terms and conditions agreed in this and other documents / agreements. \n\n

3. Prohibited Uses\n


 The Users will not use the Application:
(i)  for any purpose that is illegal;\n
(ii) to remove any copyright and other proprietary notices connection with any
    content or information on the Application;\n
(iii) to copy, decompile, reverse engineer or otherwise attempt to discover any source
        code or communication protocol,  create derivative works
based on the whole or any part of the Application, sell, assign or otherwise transfer
        any intellectual property in the Application;\n
(iv) to upload or publish any information that is infringing or unsuitable \n
(v) in any manner other than as agreed. \n\n

4. Acceptable use restrictions\n

Subject to these Terms, BPL Medtech grants to the Users a limited, personal, non-exclusive, non-assignable, and non-transferable hereof to access and
use the Application for BPL Medtech Device solely for the purposes. Users agree to use the Application
permitted by any local law and users agreed\n
that  not to copy the Application except where such copying is incidental to normal use of the Application,
or where it is necessary for the purpose of back-up or operational security; not to rent, lease, sub-license, loan, translate, merge, adapt,
 vary or modify the Application, not to make alterations to, or modifications of, the whole or any part of the Application. Or permit the Application
 or any part of it to be combines with, or become incorporated in, any other programmes.\n\n

5. Confidentiality\n

The Users acknowledges and agrees that the Application may contain information which is confidential to BPL Medtech and that the Users shall not disclose
such information or make any unauthorized use of such information. \n\n

6. Notices of infringement and takedown by BPL Medtech\n

Users finds that any of the content on the Application has been posted in violation of the Terms, or any applicable law, the User may write to
BPL Medtech at the address shown

below, giving a written statement that contains the following information as applicable:\n\n

(i) identification of the copyrighted work and/or intellectual property right claimed to
        have been infringed and the ownership of the same;\n

(ii) identification of the material that allegedly infringes or violates
        intellectual property or privacy rights, the Terms or any applicable
laws, on the Application that is requested to be removed;\n

(iii) the Users name, address, telephone number and an e-mail address, if available;\n


(iv) a statement that the User has a good faith belief that the use of the copyrighted work
        and/or exercise of the intellectual property right
is not authorized by the owner, its agent, or the law, or that the content violates the Terms
        or any applicable laws;
(v) a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and under penalty of perjury,
        that the signatory is authorized to act on
behalf of the owner of the right that is allegedly infringed; and\n


(vi) the signature of the intellectual property right owner or someone authorized
        on the owner's behalf to assert infringement of the right.\n

BPL Medtech may remove any posted submission that allegedly infringes the copyright or other
        intellectual property right of any person under Indian law within a reasonable amount of
        time as prescribed by applicable laws, upon receipt of such a statement. \n\n

7. Intellectual property Rights\n

Users acknowledge that all intellectual property rights and all content on the Application and BPL Medtech devices, including but not limited to design,
text, Application, technical drawings, configurations, graphics, other files, and their selection and arrangement are either the proprietary content
 of BPL Medtech and its  licensors, that rights in the Application are licensed (not sold) to Users, and that User have no rights in, or to, the Application
 other than the right to use the Application along with BPL Medtech Device in accordance with the terms of this Agreement.
 All rights to such content\n


 are reserved. Users acknowledge that they have no right to have access to the Application in source-code form.

Users will not challenge the validity of any of BPL Medtech intellectual property rights given pursuant to this Agreement,  or oppose any application
for the registration of such intellectual property   rights.\n

If Users suggest for any new features or functionality in the Application in BPL Medtech sole discretion, adopt into the Application, such new features
or functionality and will be the sole and exclusive property of the BPL Medtech and any and all claims of the end users as to the same are hereby waived
and released.\n\n

8. Trademarks\n

The trademarks, service marks, designs, and logos (collectively, the "Trademarks") displayed on the Application are the registered and
unregistered Trademarks of BPL Medtech and/or its licensors or affiliates. All rights to such Trademarks are reserved
\n\n


9.  Publicity\n

The User agrees that the Users will not refer to or attribute any information they publish or post in any public medium (including but not limited to
 press releases, social media, content on website and blogs) to BPL Medtech or its licensors, reproduce any Trademarks, or imply any endorsement by or
 relationship with, BPL Medtech or its licensors without the prior written permission of BPL Medtech.
\n\n


10. Disclaimers\n

The Application is provided with the understanding that BPL Medtech is not engaged in rendering professional or medical advice and services to the Consumer
or the users. All functionality on the Application is provided on an "as is," basis without warranty of any kind, either express or implied, including,
without limitation, implied warranties of

merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, title, non-infringement, and security and accuracy, as well as all warranties arising by course
 of dealing, or course of performance. BPL Medtech makes no warranties, express or implied, as to the accuracy or adequacy of the Application usage with
 BPL Medtech Devices. The User acknowledges that any reliance on any of the tools, application or transmission mechanism shall be at the User’s sole risk.
 BPL Medtech makes no guarantees of the accuracy or clinical significance of the Data collected by the Device.\n

Subject to any express warranties made in any agreement executed between the User and BPL Medtech,
        BPL Medtech makes no warranty, and
expressly disclaims any obligation that (a) the content or functionalities of the Application will be up-to-date,
        complete, comprehensive, accurate or
applicable to the Users circumstances;\n

        (b) the  Application will meet the Userss expectations or will be
        available on an uninterrupted, timely, secure,
 or error-free basis;\n

        © the results that may be obtained from the use of the Application will be accurate
        or reliable;\n

        or (d) the quality of any Devices,
 Services, Data, content, or other information and / or material obtained by the User through Application
        will meet the Users expectations.
 BPL Medtech does not endorse or represent any doctors, hospitals, partners or third party service providers
        that use this Application.\n

TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, THE APPLICATION IS PROVIDED WITHOUT ANY GUARANTEES, CONDITIONS OR WARRANTIES AS TO ITS ACCURACY,
PERFORMANCE OR UNINTERRUPTED SERVICE. BPL MEDITECH WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE CAUSED BY THE APPLICATION, A DISTRIBUTED DENIAL-OF-SERVICE
ATTACK, VIRUSES OR OTHER TECHNOLOGICALLY HARMFUL MATERIAL THAT MAY INFECT USER DEVICES, COMPUTER EQUIPMENT, COMPUTER PROGRAMS, DATA OR OTHER PROPRIETARY
MATERIAL DUE TO USE OF THE APPLICATION OR TO USER DOWNLOADING OF ANY MATERIAL POSTED ON IT, OR ON ANY WEBSITE LINKED TO IT. FURTHERMORE, TO THE EXTENT
PERMITTED BY LAW, BPL MEDITECH, AND ITS THIRD PARTIES  HEREBY EXPRESSLY EXCLUDE. \n\n

11. Third-party web sites/ content\n

This Application may provide links to third-party websites, and some of the content appearing to be on the Application may be supplied by third parties,
for example, in instances of framing of third-party websites or incorporation through framesets of content supplied by third-party servers.
If the User uses any of these external websites, he/she may be directed / redirected to such external website and may leave the Site / Application.
The Users agrees that he /she may visit any such external link, at his /her own risk, responsibility and liability. BPL Medtech makes no warranty or
representation regarding, and does not endorse, any website linked to the Site / Application or the information appearing thereon or any of the products
or services described thereon, and has no responsibility for such links or third-party websites, which are governed by the terms of use and privacy policies,
 if any, of the applicable third-party content providers. \n\n

12. Representations\n

The Users represents to BPL Medtech that:\n

(i) The User will maintain the secrecy of his/her passwords, login name/user-id and account information at all times and shall be personally
responsible for any and all use of the Application by such Users and anyone using the login information and password whether with or without the User’s
permission.\n
(ii) The Users will use the Application solely in compliance with the Terms  of the Agreement;\n
(iii) The Users will comply with all applicable laws in the use of the Application.\n
(iv) The User will not post on or about the Application and BPL Medtech Devices any materials that are threatening, libellous, defamatory, or obscene.
\n\\n
13. Termination\n

BPL Medtech may terminate, change, suspend or discontinue the Application or  Users access to the Application with or without notice to the Users.
The Users may continue to use the BPL Medtech Device for the limited purposes as per the Device user manual.
\n\n
14. Governing law and jurisdiction\n

These Terms are governed by the laws of the India without reference to the principles of conflicts of laws thereof and any disputes arising
hereof shall be exclusively determined by the Civil Courts at Bangalore City, India only.\n

If any disputes, differences, claims, etc. arise between the Parties connected with the Agreement, the same shall be resolved through
arbitration by a mutually appointed and agreed Sole Arbitrator to be appointed under the Indian Arbitration and Conciliation Act 1996.
All proceedings shall be conducted in English. The venue of arbitration shall be in Bangalore, India only.
\n\n


15  Limitation of Liability\n

BPL Medtech (including its officers, directors, employees, representatives, affiliates, partners and providers) will not be responsible
 for any injury, loss, claim, act of god, accident, delay, or any direct, special, exemplary, punitive, indirect, incidental or consequential
 damages of any kind (including without limitation lost profits or lost savings), whether based in contract, tort, strict liability or otherwise,
 that arise out of or is in any way connected with \n

        (a) any mistakes, deficiencies, failure or delay (including without limitation the use of or
 inability to use any component of the Application and Device or any breakdown on the Application and Device;\n

        (b) the performance or non-performance
 by BPL Medtech or any partner or service provider, even if BPL Medtech has been advised of the
        possibility of damages to such parties or any other
 party
        \n(d) any damages to or viruses that may infect the Users Device or other property as the result of the Users access to the Application.

Neither BPL Medtech nor its third-party content providers shall be liable for any indirect, incidental, consequential, or punitive damages
or for lost revenues or profits, whether or not advised of the possibility of such damages or losses and regardless of the theory of liability.
Liability if any shall be limited to the cost of the BPL Medtech Device only.
\n\n
16. Indemnification\n
The Users agrees to defend, indemnify and hold BPL Medtech and its affiliates’ directors, officers, employees and agents harmless from any
 and all claims, liabilities, costs and expenses, including reasonable attorneys' fees, arising in any way from the Users use of the
 Application and BPL Medtech Device, or the Users breach or violation of the law or of these Terms of this Agreement.
\n\n
17. Entire Agreement\n

These Terms, the Privacy Policy constitute the entire agreement between the parties. \n\n


18. Medical Disclaimer\n

Any content / material, including material containing medical / healthcare related information provided on the Application and BPL Meditech Device
 is for information purposes only and is not intended to replace medical advice or be a treatment for any medical condition. Whilst all reasonable
 steps have been taken to ensure the accuracy of information provided on the Application, BPL Medtech cannot itself verify the findings and materials
 which are produced by third parties and included on the Application. We encourage Users to consult a healthcare professional if they have any concerns
 about their health, are starting any health or nutritional related treatment, or for any questions Users may have regarding their own or any other
 party's medical condition. \n\n

19. Events Outside BPL Medtech Control.\n

BPL Medtech  shall not be liable or responsible for any failure to perform, or delay in performance of any of BPL Medtech obligations under this
Agreement that is caused by any act, by war, acts of public enemies, strikes or other labor disturbances, fires, floods, acts of God, or any
causes of like or different kind beyond the control of BPL Medtech, including failure of public or private telecommunications networks.
\n\n
19. QUESTIONS \n

If Users have any questions or concerns about our Terms, e-mail us at:
sales.medical@bpl.in\n
PRIVACY POLICY\n

At BPL MEDICAL TECHNOLOGIES PRIVATE LIMITED , a company incorporated and registered in India and having its registered office at 11th  KM,
Bannerghatta Road, Arakere, BANGALORE-560 076, Karnataka, India and its affiliates (“BPL Medtech”) we are committed to ensuring the privacy
of every person who shares if any information with BPL Medtech. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) read along with the terms and conditions
governing in the Agreement. \n\n

1. ACCEPTANCE OF THE POLICY AND CHANGES TO THE POLICY \n

When Users provide their Data in case needed and or applicable to us or when they click on the “I Accept” button at the end of the Terms or make
use of the Application or the Services, the Users are deemed to have consented to the collection, storage, use, processing and transfer of Data
in the manner as set out in this Privacy Policy.\n

This Privacy Policy is subject to further change. All changes to the Privacy Policy will be uploaded on this page on the Site and the same will
become effective from the date the same are uploaded. Whenever the Privacy Policy is changed Users  will be notified for their acceptance.
The Users continued use of the Site or the Application or the Services after such changes
        constitute the Users acceptance of the new terms.\n\n

2. THE INFORMATION WE GATHER \n

We may collect the Medical Data if required and or any Personal Data to access the Application and or avail the full range of services from BPL Medtech.
BPL Medtech reserve the right to cancel or refuse the Users download and /or refuse to provide the access to the Application if it is brought to BPL
Medtech notice or if it is discovered that users cannot legally binding contracts.
        In addition, Personal Data may include other items of information such as:\n

(i) Name\n
(ii) Address\n
(iii) Sex\n


(iv) Date of birth\n
(v) Contact number\n
(vi) Address\n
(vii) Email address\n
\n\n
3. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT (“PURPOSES”) \n

The Data that is collected may be used for:\n

(i) transmission to medical professionals / doctors for advisory services if required, \n
(ii) processing as may be required to enable the provision of advisory services, \n
(iii) storage on own or third party servers, \n
(iv) de-identification and use of the same for data analytics.\n
(v) Designing and improving the Application, and Services \n
(vi) Marketing and promotion \n
(vii) Communication \n\n

4. DISCLOSURE AND TRANSFER OF DATA \n

BPL Medtech may disclose and transfer Users  Data within and outside of the jurisdiction of
        the User in accordance with the following:\n

(i) We may disclose the Data to our independent contractors, vendors and suppliers including but
        not limited to telephone service providers, payment
gateway providers, web and data hosting providers (collectively, "Outside Contractors") who are engaged to provide BPL Medtech specific services and
products related to the Purposes (including services and products related to the Device).\n

(ii) We may make disclosures to our group companies.\n

(iii) We may make disclosures to third parties, in the event of a merger or acquisition,
        where all or a portion of BPL Medtech’s business or assets
(including our associated customer lists containing Personal Data) are sold or transferred to a third party.\n

(iv) We may make disclosure where required by applicable law or pursuant to summons, judicial orders, governmental investigations or proceedings, or
to establish or exercise the legal rights of BPL Medtech or defend against legal claims.\n


(v) We may make disclosures if we need to notify or assist in notifying a family member, personal representative, or another person responsible for a
Users and or Consumer care and general condition.\n
(vi) We along with the Outside Contractors reserve the right to utilize, modify, alter, revise, and / or develop the Data collected from the Users,
without compromising with the privacy and anonymity of the User. \n\n

5. CONSENT FOR USAGE OF DATA\n

User consents and permits BPL Medtech and Outside Contractors to use the Data collected
        for the following purposes only\n

(i) transmission to medical professionals / doctors for advisory services,\n
(ii) processing as may be required to enable the provision of advisory services,\n
(iii) storage on own or third party servers,\n
(iv) de-identification and use of the same for data analytics.\n
(v) Designing and improving the Application, Site and Services\n
(vi) Marketing and promotion\n
(vii) Communication\n
(viii) Collecting and refunding payments (as may be applicable)\n

BPL Medtech will use User Data for the above purposes and will not use, and/or allow third parties to use the Data for a different purpose without
getting User permission in advance.
\n\n
6. SECURITY\n

BPL Medtech takes every effort to protect against unauthorized access to individuals' Data. All Data is protected by industry standard encryption
 technologies and is handled securely within BPL Medtech. Users agree and acknowledge that they are aware that BPL Medtech has implemented such
 security measures and that such measures are adequate for the protection of their Data.\n

When we share or transfer any Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy, we will undertake reasonable efforts to ensure that the transferee maintains
or adopts security practices and


procedures which are at least as stringent as the security practices and procedures we follow.

While BPL Medtech will endeavor to take all reasonable and appropriate steps to keep secure any information which we hold about the Users and prevent
unauthorized access, the Users acknowledge that the internet is not 100% secure and that we cannot provide any absolute assurance regarding the security of Users information over the internet. BPL Medtech will not be liable in any way in relation to any breach of security and/or unintended loss or disclosure of any information.
\n\n
7. COOKIES\n

We use cookies, web beacons, web server logs and other automated means for purposes such as (i) customizing Users visits to Sites; (ii)
delivering content tailored to our Users interests and the manner in which Users browse Sites; and (iii) managing Sites and other aspects of business.
\n\n
8. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEB SITES\n

The Application may contain links to other websites and software. We are not responsible for any breach of privacy or the content of these websites or
 software. Please visit the privacy policy of these third party websites in order to understand their privacy and information collection practices.
\n\n
9. ACCESS TO USER INFORMATION\n

If Users believes that any Users Information that BPL Medtech is holding about such User (or part thereof) is incorrect or incomplete,
then Users may write to or email BPL Medtech, at this email address sales.medical@bpl.in. BPL Medtech will promptly take all reasonable
 efforts to incorporate the changes, and correct any information found to be incorrect.
\n\n
10. GRIEVANCES\n

We have nominated the Customer Support Manager at BPL Medtech as the Grievance Officer who Users may approach if they have any grievance
with respect to the processing and
\n\n

use of their Application. Users may contact this officer at  sales.medical@bpl.in.

11. COMPLIANCE WITH LAWS\n

Users are not allowed to utilise the application and or and services of BPL Medtech or engage with BPL Medtech if any of the terms of this Privacy
Policy are not in accordance with the laws applicable to such Users.  Notwithstanding anything contained in this Agreement to the contrary, the obligations
of the Users will be subject to all laws, present and future, of any government having jurisdiction over the Users, and to orders, regulations, directions or
 requests of any such government.
 \n\n

12. QUESTIONS\n

If Users have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, e-mail us at:

sales.medical@bpl.in

\n\n

BY CLICKING THE "ACCEPT" BUTTON BELOW, USERS ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THEY HAVE READ THIS TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THE AGREEMENT
ALONG WITH PRIVACY POLICY WITH  AND HAVE UNDERSTOOD IT, AND AGREE THAT THEY WILL BE BOUND BY ITS TERMS.
\n\n




</string>
    <string name="search_bio_dev">Searching for BPL iPressure BT02..</string>
    <string name="search_bpl_ipressure_">Search BPL iPressure BT02</string>
    <string name="man_p_mem">Manage Family Info</string>
    <string name="bpl_ip">BPLBeWell iPressure</string>
    <string name="bt">BT02</string>
    <string name="tap_bt">Tap on BPL iPressure BT02</string>
    <string name="tap_connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="logged_as">Primary Email</string>
    <string name="bp_ip">BPL iPressure</string>
    <string name="clinic_email">Clinic Email</string>
    <string name="sel_use_type">Select a Use Type</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="chk_up">Check Update</string>
</resources>
